omyogapages.com 2013-06-02

# Yoga Pages

## Privacy Policy

YogaPages is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement applies to all of the YogaPages Website which is operated by Prime Impact Events & Media Ltd. Company registration number UK3220574. Information is collected and held by Prime Impact in accordance with the data protection act 1984, registration number Z5020279

In some instances, YogaPages collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. YogaPages may also collect demographic information, such as your postcode and interests.

YogaPages collects and uses your personal information to operate the YogaPages website and to deliver the services you have requested. YogaPages may also use personal data to provide you with information and to conduct our own market research surveys. YogaPages does not sell, rent or lease its member lists to third parties.

Members can unsubscribe from YogaPages services at any time and can have their personal information deleted from YogaPages and other databases operated by Prime Impact events Ltd. In addition, professional members may visit the professionals area on the website to view, edit or delete their personal information from the YogaPages membership database. 

YogaPages may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Prime Impact Events & Media Ltd (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Prime Impact Events & Media Ltd including its website; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the YogaPages websites, or the public.

YogaPages keeps track, anonymously, of the pages our users visit within our websites in order to determine what pages are the most popular.

Please bear in mind that if members directly disclose personal information through discussion forums and feedback options, this information may be collected and used by others.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Phone: +44 (0)1787 224040  
Email: info@yogapages.co.uk  
Postal Address: YogaPages, Prime Impact Events & Media Ltd, The Old school, Colchester Road, Wakes Colne, Colchester, Essex CO6 2BY.

Tel 01787 224040  
Fax 01787 223535
